It was so much fun.
And a bonus.
Pretty creepy, right?
Awww...
I think it's bad.
It's bad, right?
Yeah, it is.
Oh, wow.
Extra
Extra. - Extra.
Hi, I'm Orca.
Yay!
So...
Yard talk
Yay!
This time
An amazingly nice garden
What's this?
Don Quijote.
Can I show you?
Yuzuki's
Yuzuki's favorite
It's like a rooftop.
Donkey, donkey, curtains.
Yes, I love Donkey Donkey.
So, unexpectedly...
We got together, you know.
We haven't talked about what we like lately.
Well, to be honest...
I've been getting a lot of comments from fans...
I've heard from fans
I heard that you talked about this in Staccomi.
Fans know more about it than you do.
That's right
Each one of youEach.
Well, you're right, though.
I don't know...
Everyone leaves so soon.
Yeah, we don't talk about our private lives at all.
No, we don't.
We get along well, but we don't talk at all.
But I think that's the secret of our friendship.
But I'd like to know.
I'd love to know.
What are you doing?
Yesterday and the day before.
We went to the movies.
What did you see?
RRRR.
It's kind of a hot topic.
I heard it's really good.
It's really funny.
That's funny.
It was funny from the start, and we both laughed silently the whole time.
They laughed silently for 3 hours.
I heard it was really long, like the climax of the whole show.
There are two main characters,
I fell in love with one of them, Rama.
I love him.
I love him, but seriously, that much?
It's an action/fight type of thing.
What is this, a comedy?
It's not a comedy.
But it's funny?
I don't know... the day of the fights and all... the artwork...
Artistry.
It's very well drawn.
The drawings are great.
His drawings are great, but his face is too dark.The artwork is amazing, but the faces are so intense.
The music is also amazing.
It's like 2D but 3D.
It's like a 2D movie, but it's a 3D movie, and it's so powerful that it makes you laugh.
I see what you mean. It's the kind of laughter we like.
I almost danced... just the two of us.
Under what circumstances?
We were about to start dancing.
Too much fun?
But the story is so perfect.
It's a really good story. It makes you cry.
But it's a battle, so there's a lot of sadness.
But even though it's a painful story, there are so many happy elements that you forget about it.
It's so good! It's like ours.
Like us.
I like smiling too much.
In the middle of linking with Honoka...
Oh, that's great!
It was like Honoka.
I'm sure Tahmin likes it, too.
I'm going to compare them to orcas?
I want to do a killer whale RRRR tribute!
I'm so honored!
That was so great!
I'll have to see that.
What else are you into?
You.
I'm not really into that.
You want me to get you hooked? All kinds of things.
Yuzuki is interested in a lot of things.
Lately
I'm interested, but I'm not into it.
I'm not into characters or people.
I'm more into action.
I see... going on trips...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's get into idols.
Did you hear what I said?
Yeah.
Going to live shows, going to specific meetings...
I like live shows.
I know, I know... but we're not really into the same kind of music, you know...
But I also like the kind of music you like.
But, I'm probably not the type of person who does a lot of work.
But, I mean, you like all kinds of music, don't you?
What kind of activities do you do for your "guess"?
Like going to live shows?
I don't consider myself a fan.
What do you think?
I like it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, fan, fan.
Oh, a fan?
Fan and fan are not the same thing?
I don't think so.
I think it's more like... you know...
There's like a guesser's cafe.
They have desserts and colors and stuff.
So, for example, if Yuzu's favorite is a purple girl...
I want to go to a place like that and take a picture.
Do you want to go to a place like that and take pictures?
Not so much yet.
Ahhh...
If you do that, I think I'm going to go for it.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's for sure, right?
Yeah.
I think it's bad.
It's bad, isn't it?
Yeah. - Yeah.
I kind of want you to make a guess someday, but...I'd kinda like to see you make a guess someday, but I don't know if I can.
I don't know if I can.
Well, I like Mr. Hyde and Mr. Beard, but...
I don't know, maybe it's a guess, but...
If I had to choose a guess in my life...
But I don't know...
I hear you're not a pushover like everyone else... and I've already had a couple of cups of tea with those two...
I'm not going to be a pushover like everyone else.
I want to see how it goes.
I'd like to watch.
I don't want to get too close.
I don't want to get close.
You don't think we're in the same world?
Yeah, I guess so.
I mean, I'd be thrilled to see it, of course.
I'd be thrilled to see it, and I'd be like, "Oh, he's really here.
But if it's so far away...
Oh, really? That's interesting.
I just want them to stay that way.
Are you a good fan? A good fan?
I don't want to get too involved.
Oh, so you'll remember me.
I'm going to say, "Fix it.
You're not looking for me to step in and fill in the gaps
Into their person?
Yeah.
That's so funny.
Maybe it's because you're the one they're talking to.
Oh, I see.
You're a creative person.
You're a creative person, so...
I'd like to see you let your sensibilities run free.
And when they see what you've done...
"Oh!
It's fun to see thatIt's fun to say that!
But, I mean, isn't it rather like that for you?
Your guess is as good as mine.
Maybe you're right.
I don't know...
They let me be free to do what I want.
Yes, yes, yes, objectively.
I mean...
But, you know, I'm happy to have you push me around.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it's not that I don't like either one of them.
I mean that's what my guess style is.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
So maybe
I think there are a lot of Naomi with this style.
Yes, I think there are.
It's not only those who come to buy scores, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, that's why I'm here.
I'm probably going to score.
But I'll probably go.
If there is.
Uh...
I would.
Why? What are you talking about?
If you say you'll go...
I'll just say, "I love you," and that'll be it.
Oh, I see.
They won't be bothered anymore.
What do you like about me? Don't ask him what he likes about me.
Just tell them one-sidedly.
Tell them you love them, and that might be the end of it.
Yuka, you're probably the type of fan who asks annoying questions.
Oh, really?
Yeah, so it's pretty much the opposite.
Tell me what you always buy at the convenience store.I want you to tell me what you always buy at the convenience store.
Uh...
I mean, what's your favorite food?
Hobbies, hobbies... you're probably out in the world.
You want to ask me something only you can answer? That's pretty gross.
What's creepy is that you chose to go to a convenience store.
But it's interesting because only you know about it.
And you're going to buy it? I would.
I'm dyeing it... for the girl.
So, it's different. Well, maybe it's easier to answer at a convenience store.
Really? Will it stop? I drink hot tea sometimes.
Mr. Colors.
Really?
I don't know.
I've never been asked such a weird question.
I don't know if that's weird.
I mean...
Tahmin...
Is she being nice?
Yes, she is.
It's complicated.
But that's totally fine.
But I don't want to bother you.
That's all I'm saying.
It's funny, because we don't talk about this stuff.
Really?
But I don't know, Yuzukin.
If he finds a funny video or some weird news, he sends me the URL. It always makes me laugh.
YuzukiWhen I find a funny video, I send it to the girl whose attribute I like in the video.
I send it to each member.
Haru likes YouTubers and Yuzuki likes YouTubers, so if I find a YouTuber's video that is cute or interesting, I send it to her.
Hou-chan likes anime videos. Nao, you can send me videos that I simply don't understand the meaning of, but that make me laugh.
You know, the ones that are just plain stupid. Please separate them and send them to me.
I appreciate it.
It's all in there. Really? That's great.
You got it right. It's different for everyone.I know. It depends on the person.
Hou-chan and Kanao don't reply very often.
I get reactions in spring.
I want you to keep doing that. I understand.
I will make Nao smile.
Please support me.
Thank you for watching.